Nagase.
It is you, right?
And you are Taichi, right?
Yeah.
I don't think we'll be
switching bodies that oft—
Wh-What's up?
Don't tell me...
Did you three switch bodies this time, or something?
Yes!
I'm Kiriyama Yui!
I'm Aoki Yoshifumi!
I'm Inaba Himeko!
Want some more tea?
No, thanks.
I can't take this anymore!
Why do I have to be in this totally uncute body?
Why can't I switch bodies with Iori?
Huh? With me?
I think that's the least of your worries.
Don't tell me...
Please say I'm not going to be stuck like this forever!
We can't say.
Those two were back to normal in 30 minutes.
Taichi, Iori-chan, why don't you two go to class?
You don't need to stay with us until we're back to normal.
Nah, skipping class like this is kind of fun.
It's like we're some secret society.
It's exciting!
You and your optim—
Are you... back to normal?
Looks like it.
Well, you know,
I don't really think we need to do this, but it's my job.
Could you make it look like I'm giving you the third degree?
Meanwhile, I'll be eating.
It's soba. Hate it when the noodles go soft.
You guys don't cause much trouble,
so I can't say I'm not curious.
Man, the first bite of hot food always goes down the wrong way.
Wait, is it just me?
Cut to the chase, Gotou.
You know, Inaba...
I'm trying to be a liberal, cool-with-the-kids kind of teacher,
which is why I let you guys call me Gossan,
but talking down to me is kind of...
Maybe you should learn to do your job before talking about how to do it.
Mind telling me who did our class's accounting during the cultural festival?
Thank you so much again for that.
But could you please not talk about it when other teachers are around?
What were we talking about again?
Oh, right.
So what were you guys doing?
Aoki and Kiriyama didn't show up to class until third period either.
Some mini chocolate buns we shared yesterday had gone bad, so we all came in late with upset stomachs.
That's all.
Aoki and Kiriyama are talking with Hirata-sensei right now.
Would they say the same thing?
Of course.
Well, if you say so. I got no problems with it.
You can go now.
Inaban's just amazing!
Yeah.
I don't know how she can lie through her teeth with such confidence.
You'd make a great con artist or swindler!
Seriously...
If you can't say anything nice, just shut up.
How do you think Aoki and Kiriyama are doing?
So?
Come on, Yui.
Anyone home?
What's wrong?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
I...
I'm going to the bathroom.
Have fun.
What now?
I need to find a place where I can be alone!
What the heck?!
Oh, shoot!
No other choice!
Again?!
Hello? Taichi?
Why does this have to happen to me?!
Yeah.
Is Kiriyama there?
Iori's trying to keep her sane.
Where are you?
Me?
I'm in the...
...bathroom.
You're back?
Y-Yeah.
Sorry about that.
It's okay.
Hello?!
Hello, Inaba? Can you hear me?
Why am I in the bathroom?
What did Taichi do?
Put Taichi on, right now!
Yaegashi.
We're cleaning the bathrooms today. Don't bail on me.
Bathrooms again?
You look tired.
Something happen?
No, nothing happened.
Sorry, cleaning took longer—
Taichi!
You...
You've got some explaining to do!
Wh-What?
What's wrong, Nagase?
What happened between you and Fujishima-san
yesterday when we switched bodies?!
N-Nothing important.
I'll decide if it's important or not!
Wow, Iori-chan's lost it. First time I've seen that.
Um...
I probably should've told you sooner, but...
You touched my boobs!
I've been tainted!
I didn't know what was going on!
I had to figure out somehow!
When you were in my body earlier,
you went to the girls' bathroom.
Did you...
I was just trying to find a place to hide!
Wait, that's not important right now!
The real problem...
is Fujishima-san!
A-Are you okay, Nagase?
How is the second problem worse than the first?
And seriously, what's up with Fujishima?
I never thought anyone could get Iori so worked up.
What's your class president like?
Perfect manners, perfect grades, and the teachers all love her.
She's a model student.
Who cares about that?
Taichi, how big are Iori-chan's b—
We don't have time for pointless crap like that!
But if you want to know, I'll tell you.
Iori's a C-cup.
While we're at it, I'm a B, and Yui's an A.
Wh-Why are you telling them that?!
Don't worry, Yui!
I'm sorry about your boobs,
but I love everything else about you!
Get that look off your face! It pisses me off!
And what do you mean, "sorry"?
There are times when smaller is better!
I see.
So Inaba's a B, and Kiriyama's an A.
Don't act like you're not part of the problem!
The problem right now is Fujishima-san!
What am I supposed to do?!
The problem right now is this body swapping!
Well...
hello... there.
Gotou?
How long have you been there?
I just got here.
What's with you?
Are you sick or something?
This body is perfectly fine.
This person is healthier than he needs to be.
I just don't have any real motivation, determination, resolution, enthusiasm,
or anything else along those lines.
Hey, Gossan, what's wrong?
I came here because you're confused about how you're switching personalities.
Gossan?
How do you kn—
Oh, and could you not call me Gossan or Gotou?
I'm...
not him, after all.
Then...
who are you?
Let's see, how should I answer that?
If you want a name, "Balloon Vine" is something like one for me.
"Balloon Vine"?
Why is your name the same as some obscure plant's?
Huh... Who knows?
Well, I'm something like an observer for you five.
You could say that I'm borrowing
Gotou-sensei's body right now.
In other words, you're something else in Gossan's body?
That is a good way to put it. Yes.
Then you have something to do with us switching personalities.
Well, for now,
you'll be switching personalities among the five of you at random.
You mean that both the switched personalities and the time of the switch are completely random?
Yes. Very good, Nagase-san.
It's precisely as you say.
And I will observe you while this happens.
Though, I won't watch you 24/7 for the sake of privacy.
That would require effort.
Do you all understand the situation now?
That was hardly an explanation.
Is that it? Then I have a few questions for you.
First, why us?
Next, is this whole thing under your control?
And how do we end it? What are you after?
All very good questions.
For the first question, it just so happens that you are some pretty interesting humans,
I guess.
What the heck? "Pretty interesting"?
And well, I want to watch you switch personalities
to see if anything happens that'll make me say, "Oh, that was pretty interesting."
This will all end after that.
So when this ends is under your control.
Well...
just live your lives the way you normally would.
It's best if you don't think about
how your personalities switch.
That's not what you need to do.
I also advise against telling anyone about how you're switching personalities.
That would do more harm than good.
Well, good luck.
I'm hoping for the best from around the top of my heart.
Wait!
Excuse me.
I still have plenty of questions for you.
Like I said, that's not what you need to do.
You'd better not think that everything
will go exactly the way you want!
Hey!
You...
Leave this to me!
Sorry, Gossan!
No way!
Kiriyama!
Well then, see you again.
This is just ridiculous.
Yui was a karate champion in middle school, too.
That's not the way Gossan usually moves.
And when I checked on him in the faculty room...
Me?
I was here, trying to get through this paperwork...
Huh? I haven't gotten anywhere.
Did I fall asleep or something?
It looked like he didn't know anything.
Dammit!
I don't understand any of this!
Wait, no.
If we overthink this, we might do exactly what he wants.
Should we tell someone about this?
It's probably better if we don't.
He said that it would do more harm than good, too.
Yeah.
We don't know how much of what he said was true,
but it would definitely end up being a lot of trouble.
I don't want my mom to worry about me.
The next time our personalities switch,
get in contact with the rest of us as soon as possible so we can grasp the situation.
Avoid people as much as possible.
If you run into someone, act like the person you switched with.
Got it?
Got it.
It's been a bit over a week since we agreed on that...
Just how careless can you people be?
Let's start with the most basic problem.
Raise your hand if you went into the wrong bathroom when you switched with someone of the opposite sex!
Me.
You idiots!
How could you do that?!
That's the first thing that should be on your mind!
It's a habit.
It's normal.
What's normal about it?
Someone has to say something whenever we go, thanks to you!
Um... can I make a suggestion?
Could we try going to the bathroom more often when we're not switched?
I was just talking about how it's hard going to the bathroom now.
But if one of us girls switches with Taichi or Aoki and has to go to the bathroom,
we have to...
No!
She's overdoing it with the rejection.
No! No! No!
Okay. Aoki and I will make sure we do that.
Thanks.
Why are you so nice to Taichi?!
No need to make a big deal out of it.
I've already learned how to pee standing up.
That's a big deal if you ask me.
And are you being serious right now?
More importantly, what about our purity?
Are our bodies safe?
Perfectly. Right, Aoki?
Yeah.
Honestly, when I'm in a girl's body, there are a few things I'd like to try,
but you're perfectly safe.
I haven't had to go to the bathroom yet, either.
You sure about that?
Totally sure!
It's times like these when we have to trust each other.
I won't do anything stupid like that.
Yeah, you're right.
Hey, Iori, when I switched with you a few nights ago, no one was home but you.
Why's that?
I was thinking that it might be dangerous to leave a girl at home alone.
Oh, that?
I never told you, but my parents are divorced and I live with my mom.
Oh, and my mom is really busy.
But if someone were to break in,
I'd just let loose on him with a can of pepper spray, then beat the crap out of him!
It's okay!
It's not okay at all!
You're in the most danger when you're complacent like that!
Once it happens, it's too late!
Oh...
Um...
Sorry.
Me too.
I'm... sorry.
How long is this going to go on for?
Who is this Balloon Vine?
Wow. So this is how Aoki sees the world?
He's really tall!
Wait... Nagase?
Right!
Oh? Yui looks so tiny!
S-Sorry!
It's not like I mind when you touch me.
It's just that you're in Aoki's body right now, so I jumped back.
I know, I know.
I shouldn't have tried to touch you in the first place.
Looks like this personality switch is a long one.
Something wrong, Nagase?
I messed up.
You mean that thing with Kiriyama?
Or are you worried about something else?
Is it anything I can help you with?
Now it's Taichi's turn on Nagase Iori's Question Time!
What?
Everyone implicitly believes that we each have a soul, a consciousness, or a personality,
and that they make us who we are.
This is why you would identify a combination of Aoki's body and Nagase Iori's soul as Nagase Iori.
But souls, or personalities, are neither tangible nor visible.
This is why we identify a person by their own physical body.
Basically, our bodies are the essence of our identities.
But what if our bodies, through personality switching, for example, were no longer solely our own?
Would we still be ourselves?
Nagase?
Just kidding.
Oh, Taichi!
W-Welcome back.
Finally!
I'm back in my own body!
It was like Nagase wasn't her usual self.
Though, I'm probably overthinking it.
So that's the way the wind is blowing.
What do you mean, "the wind is blowing"?
What're you talking about?
Oh, it's nothing.
Attention, everyone!
We need three volunteers from our class to participate in this month's city clean-up.
Anyone willing to do it?
Oh, come on. Seriously?
Gossan probably just volunteered our class to get out of a meeting.
I'm busy with my club. I can't do it!
Okay, okay. Settle down.
I'll be one of the three, so we just need two more.
I'll do it.
Inaba-san? You're volunteering?
I...
I'll do it too.
Okay.
Stop that.
Have fun, Taichi!
Get off me.
I'm having a wonderful day, thanks to you.
I'll make it up to you later, so please forgive me, Inaba-san.
Yaegashi-kun, can I ask you a question?
I'll be frank.
What's your relationship with Nagase-san?
Are you just in the same club?
Or...
Well, let's see.
I suppose I should make it perfectly clear to you.
Hey, what are you saying?
Iori's my woman!
Keep your hands off her!
I'm in love with Nagase?
Whenever a guy comes close, your body starts shaking.
The way you're looking at me is kind of scary...
Don't worry. Just leave it to me.
Okay.
If that's what you want, Mom.
Selfless freak.